articlestars.com 2015-09-19

# Article Directory Submission | Submit Quality Original Articles - ArticleStars.Com

Your ArticleStars Directory Privacy Policy

ArticleStars.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet

technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We

may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street

address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will

never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party.

Period.

How we gather information from users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting,

the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For

example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access

to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or

when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate

in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other

interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, ArticleStars.com also collects

information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may

be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your

Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold

information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user

name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each

time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular

advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may

also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose

not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse

to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of

the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may

not be able to customize the sites features according to your preferences.

What we do with the information we collect

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and

deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and

do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you)

may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about

your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help

enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or

what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be

shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does

not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to

identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on

www.ArticleStars.com to communicate with you about your registration and

customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and

products offered by www.ArticleStars.com and other topics we think you might

find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by ArticleStars.com may also

be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration,

troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of

sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third

parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web

hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your

information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we

continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other

companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among

the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a

court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so

by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or

to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary.

Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements

ArticleStars.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect

the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our

partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through

our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.

For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a

frame on a www.ArticleStars.com page, certain content that is actually created or

hosted by a third party. Also, through ArticleStars.com you may be introduced to,

or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes

offered by other parties. ArticleStars.com is not responsible for the actions or

policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of

those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a

third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may

use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences

or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served

by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine

whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features

available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use

cookies or other technology to gather information. ArticleStars.com does not

control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and

is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable

Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed

publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge

and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.

Such activities are beyond the control of ArticleStars and this policy.

Children

ArticleStars.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable

Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we

discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation

of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe

ArticleStars.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please

contact us at the address listed below.

Contacting Us

We can be reached by emailing us.

Changes to this Policy

ArticleStars.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please

check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following

the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used

according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was

collected.

Governing law

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by New York law. If a dispute

arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a

mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Buffalo. Any costs and

fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally

by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through

mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following

location: Buffalo, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association.

Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any

court with jurisdiction to do so.

This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not

create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**Your ArticleStars Directory Privacy Policy**  
ArticleStars.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internettechnology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. Wemay use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, streetaddress, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We willnever sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party.Period.

**How we gather information from users**  
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting,the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. Forexample, you may be asked to provide information when you register for accessto certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters orwhen you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participatein sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and otherinteractive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, ArticleStars.com also collectsinformation automatically and through the use of electronic tools that maybe transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of yourInternet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and holdinformation from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your username and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information eachtime you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particularadvertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we mayalso gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choosenot to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuseto accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions ofthe site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we maynot be able to customize the sites features according to your preferences.

**What we do with the information we collect**  
Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit anddeliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy anddo not share your information with anyone.  
Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you)may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information aboutyour usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to helpenhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most orwhat features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally beshared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information doesnot include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to  
identify you individually.  
We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected onwww.ArticleStars.com to communicate with you about your registration andcustomization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services andproducts offered by www.ArticleStars.com and other topics we think you mightfind of interest.  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by ArticleStars.com may alsobe used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration,troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration ofsweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain thirdparties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Webhosting service for example) may access such information. We will use yourinformation only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as wecontinue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with othercompanies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be amongthe transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to acourt order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do soby law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/orto law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary.Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements**  
ArticleStars.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respectthe privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including ourpartners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible throughour site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of aframe on a www.ArticleStars.com page, certain content that is actually created orhosted by a third party. Also, through ArticleStars.com you may be introduced to,or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakesoffered by other parties. ArticleStars.com is not responsible for the actions orpolicies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies ofthose third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by athird party.  
While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties mayuse cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferencesor retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is servedby third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determinewhether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features  
available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may usecookies or other technology to gather information. ArticleStars.com does notcontrol the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, andis not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.  
You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally IdentifiableInformation on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewedpublicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledgeand may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.Such activities are beyond the control of ArticleStars and this policy.

**Children**  
ArticleStars.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally IdentifiableInformation from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If wediscover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violationof this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believeArticleStars.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, pleasecontact us at the address listed below.

**Contacting Us**  
We can be reached by emailing us.

**Changes to this Policy**  
ArticleStars.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Pleasecheck this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site followingthe posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be usedaccording to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information wascollected.

**Governing law**  
This policy and the use of this Site are governed by New York law. If a disputearises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of amutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Buffalo. Any costs andfees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equallyby each of us.  
If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution throughmediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the followinglocation: Buffalo, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association.Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in anycourt with jurisdiction to do so.  
This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do notcreate any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
